{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Deck Cleaning \u0026 Sealing Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40205/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40205,"taskName":"Deck, Fence, Patio or Porch - Clean and Seal","taskDescription":"Clean and Seal Decks, Fences, Patios, Drives, or Porches","xmTaskDescriptor":"Deck Cleaning \u0026 Sealing Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":291,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Clean Fence deck Seal Patios","textMessagingName":"Clean/Seal Deck","rolloverLongDesc":"Powerwashing removes mold, algae, moss, etc. \u0026 the sealant helps protect the surface from water damage \u0026 makes it easier to clean in the future. Note separate category for powerwashing only.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes powerwashing \u0026 application of sealant.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean and Seal Decks, Fences, Patios, Drives, or Porches.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Deck Cleaning \u0026 Sealing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Clean, Seal or Waterproof Decks, Patios, Fences","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":17,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean \u0026 Seal Deck, Fence, Patio or Porch","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Deck, Fence, Patio or Porch - Clean and Seal","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Deck or Porch Project","urlName":"Deck-Fence-Patio-or-Porch-Clean-and-Seal","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Deck Cleaning \u0026 Sealing Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Decks, Patios, Fences","searchKeywords":"Clean,Fence,deck,Seal,Patios,vinyl,designs,pool,,tub,hot,wood,driveway,drive,cedar,yard,back,Decks,Patio,Porch","emcCategoryOid":-12017,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":512,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40205/":{"taskOID":40205,"originalTaskOID":40205,"setID":512,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4691,"questionDisplayText":"Surface To Clean \u0026 Seal","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of surface(s) do you need to be cleaned and sealed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2406,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fence","answerDisplayText":"Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5011,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Railings","answerDisplayText":"Railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5397,"questionDisplayText":"Treatment Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What treatments would you like to have done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1408,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clean","answerDisplayText":"Clean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4846,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power/Pressure wash","answerDisplayText":"Power/Pressure wash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Seal/Finish","answerDisplayText":"Seal/Finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5927,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Special coating","answerDisplayText":"Special coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5592,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Set nails/screws","answerDisplayText":"Set nails/screws","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4691,"questionDisplayText":"Surface To Clean \u0026 Seal","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of surface(s) do you need to be cleaned and sealed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2406,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fence","answerDisplayText":"Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5011,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Railings","answerDisplayText":"Railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2406,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fence","answerDisplayText":"Fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5011,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Railings","answerDisplayText":"Railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5397,"questionDisplayText":"Treatment Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What treatments would you like to have done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1408,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clean","answerDisplayText":"Clean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4846,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power/Pressure wash","answerDisplayText":"Power/Pressure wash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Seal/Finish","answerDisplayText":"Seal/Finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5927,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Special coating","answerDisplayText":"Special coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5592,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Set nails/screws","answerDisplayText":"Set nails/screws","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1408,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clean","answerDisplayText":"Clean","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4846,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power/Pressure wash","answerDisplayText":"Power/Pressure wash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Seal/Finish","answerDisplayText":"Seal/Finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5927,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Special coating","answerDisplayText":"Special coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5592,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Set nails/screws","answerDisplayText":"Set nails/screws","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}